[{
    "question":"Name That Author: Who wrote The Iliad?",
    "answer_1":"Euripides",
    "answer_2":"Beowulf",
    "answer_3":"Homer",
    "answer_4":"Virgil",
    "right_answer":"Homer",
    "img":"literature-images/qst1.jfif"
},

{
    "question":" John Donne is known as a member of which school of poetry?",
    "answer_1":"Romanticism",
    "answer_2":"Jacobean",
    "answer_3":"Georgian",
    "answer_4":"Metaphysical",
    "right_answer":"Metaphysical",
    "img":"literature-images/qst2.jfif"
},

{
    "question":" John Milton’s Paradise Lost was written during which century?",
    "answer_1":"1400’s",
    "answer_2":"1500’s",
    "answer_3":" 1600’s",
    "answer_4":"1700’s",
    "right_answer":"1700’s",
    "img":"literature-images/qst3.jfif"

},

{
    "question":"Sir Walter Scott is known for his historical novels about which country?",
    "answer_1":"Ireland",
    "answer_2":"Scotland",
    "answer_3":"Wales",
    "answer_4":"England",
    "right_answer":"Scotland",
    "img":"literature-images/qst4.jfif"

},
{
    "question":" Who is the heroine of Nathaniel Hawthorne’s The Scarlet Letter?",
    "answer_1":"Anne Hutchinson",
    "answer_2":" Emily Shelby",
    "answer_3":"Agnes Grey",
    "answer_4":"Hester Prynne",
    "right_answer":"Hester Prynne",
    "img":"literature-images/qst5.jfif"

},
{
    "question":"Who wrote The Electric Kool-Aid Acid Test?",
    "answer_1":"William S. Burroughs",
    "answer_2":" Hunter S. Thompson",
    "answer_3":"Ken Kesey",
    "answer_4":"Tom Wolfe",
    "right_answer":"Tom Wolfe",
    "img":"literature-images/qst6.jfif"

},

{
    "question":"Who is the protagonist of James Joyce’s Ulysses?",
    "answer_1":"Leopold Bloom",
    "answer_2":"Leopold Ulysses",
    "answer_3":"Ulysses Bloom",
    "answer_4":"Homer Bloom",
    "right_answer":"Leopold Ulysses",
    "img":"literature-images/qst7.jfif"
},

{
    "question":"Name That Author: Who wrote the noir classic The Maltese Falcon?",
    "answer_1":"James Ellory",
    "answer_2":"Dashiell Hammett",
    "answer_3":"James M. Cain",
    "answer_4":"Raymond Chandler",
    "right_answer":"Dashiell Hammett",
    "img":"literature-images/qst8.jfif"
},

{
    "question":"Which is NOT a poem by Emily Dickinson?",
    "answer_1":"Hope’ is the thing with feathers",
    "answer_2":"Because I could not stop for Death",
    "answer_3":"Acquainted with the night",
    "answer_4":"I felt a Funeral, in my Brain",
    "right_answer":"Acquainted with the night",
    "img":"literature-images/qst9.jfif"
},

{
    "question":"Who wrote Romeoo and Juliet",
    "answer_1":"William Shakespeare",
    "answer_2":"Anne-Laure Chat",
    "answer_3":"Germaine Landre",
    "answer_4":"Gisèle Venet",
    "right_answer":"William Shakespeare",
    "img":"literature-images/qst10.jfif"
}

]